znetindia.net 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | ZNetLive

## Privacy Policy

This privacy statement describes how ZNET Technologies Private Limited collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website: [ZNetLive.com.](https://www.znetlive.com/) It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

## Collection and Use Of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address and phone number.
  * Billing Information such as payment mode details and billing address (we seek payment mode and billing details from customer for verifying his payment detail to deliver the service).
  * If you are registering on behalf of your organization, your company's name, mailing address, and other company information, as deemed necessary for the purpose of providing services.

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. 

We use the information we collect to:

  * Respond to customer service & offer requests.
  * Administer your account.
  * Improve our website and marketing efforts.

## Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our emails by logging into your account and update your notification selections or you can contact us at [billing@znetlive.com.](mailto:legal@znetlive.com) We enable you to create an account, and share information such as messages, offers and requests with others.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use the email address you used to register to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect of your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [billing@znetlive.com](mailto:legal@znetlive.com)

## Information Sharing 

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service (such as utilizing our 'Live Chat' feature). These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * As required by law such as to comply with any legal process. 
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * If ZNet Technologies Private Limited is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or use of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

##  Tracking Technologies 

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by ZNet Technologies Private Limited and our business partners, affiliates, or analytics. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g. language preference) and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. 

##  Behavioral Targeting/Re-Targeting 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by logging into your account and updating your notification selections or you can contact us at [billing@znetlive.com.](mailto:legal@znetlive.com) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

##  Links To Other Websites

Our Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of ZNet Technologies Private Limited. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

##  Security 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or net banking details etc.) while filling order forms, you are redirected to the website of payment gateway, which has its own Privacy Policy and it shall be presumed that before completing the process of payment you have carefully gone through the Privacy Policy of the Payment Gateway. We do not receive any detail regarding your credit card, bank account, debit card etc. from the payment gateway or otherwise. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [billing@znetlive.com](mailto:legal@znetlive.com)

##  Additional Policy Information

Our website includes widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs & community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas might be read, collected, and/or used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [billing@znetlive.com.](mailto:legal@znetlive.com) In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

## Testimonials 

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customer on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at [billing@znetlive.com](mailto:legal@znetlive.com)

## Correcting, Deleting And Updating Your Personal Information 

To ensure the accuracy of your information, you may change/update personal information by logging to your account or by contacting us directly at [billing@znetlive.com. ](mailto:legal@znetlive.com) You may change/update your contact information except email ID and country. To change email ID, you are required to follow the process and provide necessary information as sought, by contacting our billing/support staff or by raising ticket from registered email ID only mentioning purpose. We don't permit the client to change country. However, it is only possible when you are shifting your business location to different country and for that, you need to share all required details sought by us. 

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [billing@znetlive.com. ](mailto:legal@znetlive.com) We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Notification Of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. We encourage and advice you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

## Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below: **ZNet Technologies Private Limited,** D-10/52, Chitrakoot, Vaishali Nagar Jaipur Rajasthan 302021 India 91-141-4070666 Email: [billing@znetlive.com](mailto:legal@znetlive.com)
